<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Rudolf J</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Rudolf J</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deployment of machine learning algorithms to predict sepsis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/sepsis-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/sepsis-deployment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A practical study on deploying machine learning algorithms for sepsis prediction in real-world clinical settings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development and implementation of digital solutions in healthcare: insights from the Australian tertiary hospital landscape</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/example-publication-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/example-publication-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An in-depth examination of digital health implementation strategies in Australian tertiary care settings, providing insights for healthcare organizations undergoing digital transformation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>False hope of a single generalisable AI sepsis prediction model: bias and proposed mitigation strategies for improving performance based on a retrospective multisite cohort study</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/example-publication-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/example-publication-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A critical analysis of AI sepsis prediction models revealing the challenges of generalization across healthcare settings and proposing evidence-based strategies for improved performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperkalaemia among hospital admissions: prevalence, risk factors, treatment and impact on length of stay</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/example-publication-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/example-publication-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A comprehensive analysis of hyperkalaemia in hospitalized patients, examining prevalence, risk factors, and clinical outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation frameworks for end-to-end clinical AI: derivation of the SALIENT framework</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/salient-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/salient-framework/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Introduction of the SALIENT framework for systematic implementation of clinical AI solutions from development to deployment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposing a novel Seriously Deteriorated Patient Indicator (SDPI) for hospitalised ward patients</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/example-publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/example-publication/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This preprint introduces a novel indicator system for identifying seriously deteriorated patients in hospital ward settings, aiming to improve early detection and intervention strategies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
